Guide to the ACT UP New York records, 1969, 1982-1997 [bulk 1987-1995]
The New York Public Library. Manuscripts and Archives Division.
- Series VIII. Subjects, 1982-1995, n.d.; 556812; 40 boxes
  - New York City, 557047
    - Budget crisis, 1991 May-Jul; 557053 (Reel 77, Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Condom controversy, 1990; 557054 (Reel 77, Box 99, Folder 2-4)
    - Health Commissioner, 1990; 557055; Woodrow A. Myers, Jr. (Reel 77, Box 99, Folder 5-6)
    - Public schools AIDS education, 1992; 557056 (Reel 77, Box 99, Folder 7)
  - New York State's response to AIDS/HIV, 1988-1991; 557057 (Reel 78, Box 100, Folder 5-8)
  - Nureyev, Rudolf, n.d.; 557058 (Reel 79, Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Nutrition, n.d.; 557059 (Reel 79, Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Obituaries, 557060
    - A-C, n.d.; 557061 (Reel 79, Box 101, Folder 3)
    - D-F, n.d.; 557062 (Reel 79, Box 101, Folder 4)
    - G-I, n.d.; 557063 (Reel 79, Box 101, Folder 5)
    - J-L, n.d.; 557064 (Reel 79, Box 101, Folder 6)
    - M-P, n.d.; 557065 (Reel 79, Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Q-S, n.d.; 557066 (Reel 79, Box 101, Folder 8)
    - T, n.d.; 557067 (Reel 79, Box 101, Folder 9)
    - U-Z, n.d.; 557068 (Reel 79, Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Unidentified, n.d.; 557069 (Reel 79, Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Parasites, n.d.; 557070 (Reel 79, Box 101, Folder 12-14)
  - The Partnership for the Homeless, Inc., n.d.; 557071 (Reel 79, Box 101, Folder 15)
  - Pediatrics, 557072
    - Children and AIDS, 557073
      - 1983-1986, 557074 (Reel 79, Box 101, Folder 16-18)
      - 1987-1988, 557075 (Reel 79, Box 102, Folder 1-5)
      - 1989-1991, 557076 (Reel 80, Box 102, Folder 6-10)
      - n.d, 557077 (Reel 80, Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Youth, 1992; 557078 (Reel 80, Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Perot, Ross, n.d.; 557079 (Reel 80, Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Pharmaceutical companies, n.d.; 557080; General information (Reel 80, Box 103, Folder 3-4)
  - Philadelphia, circa 1993; 557081; Regarding the film starring Tom Hanks and Denzel Washington. (Reel 81, Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Philanthropy, n.d.; 557082 (Reel 81, Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Politicians, n.d.; 557083; General information (Reel 81, Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Press project, 1992; 557084 (Reel 81, Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Primaries, 1992; 557085 (Reel 81, Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Primates, n.d.; 557086; Research (Reel 81, Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Prostitutes, n.d.; 557087 (Reel 82, Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Psychiatric issues, n.d.; 557088 (Reel 82, Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Public Broadcasting System (PBS), n.d.; 557089 (Reel 82, Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Public sex spaces, n.d.; 557090 (Reel 83, Box 105, Folder 11-12)
  - Queer Nation, 1993; 557091 (Reel 83, Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Red, Hot, and Blue, 1992-1993; 557092 (Reel 83, Box 105, Folder 15-16)
  - Republican National Convention, 1992 Summer; 557093 (Reel 84, Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Rivera, Julio, n.d.; 557094; Press clippings on Julio Rivera's murder (Reel 84, Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Safer sex (AIDS) including condoms, 557095; Press clippings (Reel 84, Box 106, Folder 9)
  - St. Patrick's Day, 1992-1993; 557096 (Reel 84, Box 106, Folder 10-11)
  - Shalala, Donna, n.d.; 557097 (Reel 85, Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Smithson, Frank: Contracts, n.d.; 557098 (Reel 85, Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Strategy planning weekend, 1993 Jan 9-10; 557099; Located at the Gay and Lesbian Community Center in New York City/ (Reel 85, Box 107, Folder 16)
  - Students Taking Action for a New Direction (STAND), 557100 (Reel 85, Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Terence Cardinal Cooke Health Care Center, n.d.; 557101 (Reel 85, Box 107, Folder 18-19)
  - Testing, 557102
    - 1992, 557103 (Reel 86, Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Disclosure, 557104
      - Articles, 1991-1994; 557105 (Reel 86, Box 108, Folder 3-8)
      - Correspondence and related materials, 557106 (Reel 85, Box 108, Folder 1-2)
    - Tracing, n.d.; 557107 (Reel 86, Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Texas, 557108
    - Healthcare issues, n.d.; 557109 (Reel 86, Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Houston convention, 1992 Aug; 557110 (Reel 85, Box 107, Folder 17)
  - Treatment, 557111
    - Drugs for AIDS, n.d.; 557112 (Reel 86, Box 108, Folder 12-14)
    - Research, 557113
      - 1987-1988, 557114 (Reel 86, Box 109, Folder 1)
      - 1989-1991, 557115 (Reel 87, Box 109, Folder 2-6)
      - n.d, 557116 (Reel 88, Box 110, Folder 1-3)
      - Seventh International Conference on AIDS, Florence, Italy, 1991 Jun; 557117 (Reel 87, Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Tumor necrosis factor, n.d.; 557118 (Reel 88, Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Unique identifier pilot program and related materials, 557119 (Reel 88, Box 110, Folder 14)
  - United for AIDS Action (UAA), 1993; 557120 (Reel 89, Box 111, Folder 1)
  - US immigration policy, 1988-1993; 557121 (Reel 89, Box 111, Folder 2-4)
  - Universal access to benefits: Federal government, n.d.; 557122 (Reel 89, Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Vaccines, 1989-1993; 557123 (Reel 89, Box 111, Folder 6-9)
  - Venereal disease, n.d.; 557124 (Reel 89, Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Violence in the family, n.d.; 557125 (Reel 89, Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Vitamin C, n.d.; 557126 (Reel 89, Box 111, Folder 12-13)
  - West Virginia: Health and insurance issues, 557127 (Reel 89, Box 111, Folder 14)
  - Williams, Enoch, n.d.; 557128 (Reel 89, Box 111, Folder 15)
  - Wisconsin: Health and insurance issues, 557129 (Reel 89, Box 111, Folder 16)
  - Women, 557130
    - AIDS/HIV, 557131
      - Disease, 1986-1990; 557132 (Reel 90, Box 113, Folder 2)
      - Research, 557133
        - 1986-1990, 557134 (Reel 90, Box 113, Folder 3-6)
        - Pregnancy, 1986-1990; 557135 (Reel 90, Box 113, Folder 7)
        - Volume I, 1986-1990; 557136 (Reel 90, Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Health issues, 557137
      - 1987-1989, 557138 (Reel 89, Box 111, Folder 17-18)
      - 1990-1991, 557139 (Reel 89, Box 112, Folder 1-6)
      - 1991-1993, 557140 (Reel 90, Box 112, Folder 7-10)
  - Workers compensation, n.d.; 557141 (Reel 90, Box 112, Folder 11)
  - World Health Organization (WHO), n.d.; 557142 (Reel 90, Box 112, Folder 14)
- Series IX. Conferences, 1983-1994; 557143; 20 boxes
  Series IX. Conferences is arranged alphabetically by conference title. The series contains documentation of some of the conferences attended by ACT UP representatives. Included are addresses, correspondence, bulletins and newsletters, handouts, notes, press clippings, programs and abstracts, reports, and serials.
  The most documented conferences are the international conferences that enabled activists, physicians, medical researchers, public health officials, pharmaceutical corporations, and interested parties to meet and exchange ideas about the latest developments in AIDS/HIV research, social concerns, and related issues. The international conferences represented are the third through tenth International Conference on AIDS, as well as the seventh and eighth International Conference on AIDS in Africa/African Conference on Sexually Transmitted Diseases. The remainder of this series contains a representative sample of other conferences. See Series XV. Addenda for additional conference materials.
  - ACT UP AIDS Conference, 1990; 557144 (Reel 102, Box 132, Folder 1)
  - AIDS, The New York Academy of Sciences, 1983 Nov; 557145 (Reel 101, Box 131, Folder 3-5)
  - AIDS Treatment Activists Conference (ATAC). Technical manual, 1990 Nov 10-11; 557146 (Reel 102, Box 132, Folder 2)
  - First International Indigenous Peoples of the Land Coming Together, HIV/AIDS Conference, Auckland, Aotearoa/New Zealand, 1992 Mar 16-20; 557147 (Reel 101, Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Fourth International Conference on Social Work and AIDS, Washington, DC, 1992; 557148 (Reel 101, Box 131, Folder 9)
  - International Conference on AIDS, 557149
    - Third International Conference on AIDS, Washington, DC, 1987 Jun 1-5; 557150 (Reel 91, Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Fourth International Conference on AIDS, Stockholm, Sweden, 1988 Jun12-16; 557151
      - Abstracts, 557152
        - A-E, 557153 (Reel 91, Box 114, Folder 6-10)
        - F-G, 557154 (Reel 91, Box 114, Folder 11)
        - H-I, 557155 (Reel 91, Box 114, Folder 12)
      - Book I: Final program, 557156; Not microfilmed (Box 115, Folder 5)
      - Book II: Programs and abstracts, 557157; Not microfilmed (Box 115, Folder 6)
      - Book II: Programs and abstracts, 557158; Photocopies (Reel 91, Box 115, Folder 2-3)
      - Book II: Programs and abstracts, 557159; Photocopies (Reel 92, Box 115, Folder 4)
      - Exhibition catalogue, Face of AIDS sessions, list of participants, 557160 (Reel 91, Box 114, Folder 2)
      - List by section, 557161 (Reel 91, Box 114, Folder 5)
      - Plenary topics, 557162 (Reel 91, Box 114, Folder 4)
      - Preliminary program, 557163 (Reel 91, Box 115, Folder 1)
      - World Health Organization. Global AIDS Fact File., 557164 (Reel 91, Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Fifth International Conference on AIDS: The Scientific and Social Challenge, Montréal, Canada, 1989 Jun 4-9; 557165; See Series XV. Addenda for additional materials.
      - Abstracts, 557166; Not microfilmed (Box 116, Folder 4)
      - ACT UP, 557167
        - Media report: ACT UP Takes Over Montreal, 557168 (Reel 92, Box 117, Folder 2-3)
        - A National AIDS Treatment Research Agenda, 557169; Preliminary and final versions (Reel 92, Box 117, Folder 4)
        - Press releases, 557170 (Reel 92, Box 117, Folder 5-6)
      - Addresses, 557171
        - Joseph, Stephen C., Commissioner of Health, New York City, 557172 (Reel 92, Box 117, Folder 8)
        - Kaunda, Kenneth David, President of the Republic of Zambia, 557173 (Reel 92, Box 117, Folder 7)
        - Mann, Jonathan M., MD, MPH. "Global AIDS into the 1990s.", 557174 (Reel 92, Box 117, Folder 9)
      - Handouts, 557175 (Reel 93, Box 118, Folder 8-10)
      - Information, 557176
        - Conference, 557177 (Reel 92, Box 116, Folder 2)
        - General, 557178; Information by and for ACT UP members attending the conference. (Reel 92, Box 116, Folder 3)
      - Newspaper/press clippings, 557179 (Reel 93, Box 118, Folder 2-6)
      - Pamphlets, 557180 (Reel 93, Box 118, Folder 7)
      - Press releases, 557181 (Reel 93, Box 118, Folder 1)
      - Programme, 557182; Not microfilmed (Box 116, Folder 5)
      - Registration and call for abstracts, 557183 (Reel 92, Box 116, Folder 1)
      - Related material, 557184
        - Center for Disease Control, 557185
          - America Responds to AIDS, 1989; 557186 (Reel 92, Box 117, Folder 12)
          - Information about Sex and AIDS, 557187 (Reel 92, Box 117, Folder 12)
      - Reports, 557188
        - SIDA 1989, 557189 (Reel 92, Box 117, Folder 11)
        - Le silence fait la mor[te] vive la vie; agissons aujourd'hui!, 1989; 557190 (Reel 92, Box 117, Folder 1)
        - Tabular Information on Legal Instruments Dealing with AIDS and HIV Infection, circa 1989; 557191 (Reel 92, Box 117, Folder 10)
      - Serials, 1989; 557192 (Reel 93, Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Sixth International Conference on AIDS: AIDS in the Nineties: From Science to Policy, San Francisco, California, 1990 Jun 19-24; 557193
      - ACT UP Treatment and Data committee. AIDS Treatment Research Agenda, 1990; 557194 (Reel 93, Box 119, Folder 3)
      - Call for abstracts and registration, 557195 (Reel 93, Box 119, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 557196 (Reel 93, Box 119, Folder 1)
      - Newspaper clippings, 557197
        - circa 1990, 557198 (Reel 93, Box 119, Folder 5-8)
        - circa 1990, 557199 (Reel 94, Box 119, Folder 9-11)
        - circa 1990, 557200 (Reel 94, Box 120, Folder 1-8)
        - circa 1990, 557201 (Reel 94, Box 121, Folder 1-6)
        - circa 1990, 557202 (Reel 95, Box 121, Folder 7-11)
        - circa 1990, 557203 (Reel 95, Box 122, Folder 1-8)
        - circa 1990, 557204 (Reel 96, Box 122, Folder 9-13)
        - circa 1990, 557205 (Reel 96, Box 123, Folder 1-14)
        - circa 1990, 557206 (Reel 96, Box 124, Folder 1-8)
      - Stanley, Peter. ACT UP: Past, Present, and Future., 557207 (Reel 93, Box 119, Folder 4)
      - Survey and Opening ceremony program, 1990 Mar, Jun 20; 557208; This folder contains a survey of AIDS as an international human rights issue entitled Double Jeopardy -- Threat to Life and Human Rights: Discrimination against persons with AIDS. Cambridge, MA: Human Rights Internet, 1990, written by Roberta Cohen and Laurie S. Wiseberg. (Reel 96, Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Seventh International Conference on AIDS: Science Challenging AIDS, Florence, Italy, 1991 Jun 16-21; 557209
      - Abstract books, vol. I-II, 557210 (Reel 97, Box 125, Folder 3-4)
      - ACT UP reports and the Treatment and Data committee's AIDS Treatment Research Agenda, 557211 (Reel 97, Box 125, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous materials, 557212 (Reel 97, Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Eighth International Conference on AIDS/Third Sexually Transmitted Disease World Congress: A World United Against AIDS, Amsterdam, The Netherlands, 1992 Jul 19-24; 557213
      - Abstracts, 557214
        - New call for abstracts and registration, 557215 (Reel 97, Box 126, Folder 1)
        - Final program and oral abstracts, vol. I, 557216 (Reel 98, Box 126, Folder 6)
        - Poster abstracts, vol. II, 557217 (Reel 98, Box 126, Folder 7)
      - ACT UP, 557218
        - Information guide including reports by the International Conference committee, 557219 (Reel 97, Box 126, Folder 4)
        - News from the Amsterdam AIDS Conference, 557220 (Reel 97, Box 126, Folder 2)
        - Treatment and Data committee: Notes from George M. Carter, 557221 (Reel 97, Box 126, Folder 3)
      - Bulletins, 557222; Assorted bulletins from the conference (Reel 99, Box 127, Folder 6)
      - Conference summary reports and related material, 557223; Includes the conference's Daily Planner and Exhibition Guide. Contents not microfilmed. (Box 126, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1991-1992; 557224 (Reel 98, Box 127, Folder 1)
      - Delegates information, 557225 (Reel 98, Box 127, Folder 2)
      - Photographs and negatives, 557226; Not microfilmed (Box 127, Folder 9)
      - Poster presentation, 557227 (Reel 98, Box 127, Folder 5)
      - Reports, 557228
        - circa 1992, 557229 (Reel 98, Box 127, Folder 3)
        - Gonsalves, Gregg, and Mark Harrington. AIDS Research at the NIH: A critical review., circa 1992; 557230 (Reel 98, Box 127, Folder 4)
      - World AIDS News, 557231 (Reel 99, Box 127, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous materials, circa 1992; 557232 (Reel 99, Box 127, Folder 8)
    - Ninth International Conference on AIDS/Fourth Sexually Transmitted Disease World Congress: Berlin, Germany, 1993 Jun 6-11; 557233
      - Abstract book, vol. II, 557234 (Reel 99, Box 128, Folder 5-6)
      - Call for abstracts and registration, vol. I, 557235 (Reel 99, Box 128, Folder 2-4)
      - Contacts, 557236 (Reel 99, Box 129, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 1992-1993; 557237 (Reel 99, Box 129, Folder 1-2)
      - Newsletters, 557238
        - Conference news, 557239 (Reel 100, Box 129, Folder 8)
        - Global AIDS Needs, 557240 (Reel 100, Box 129, Folder 9)
        - HIV Focus, 557241 (Reel 100, Box 129, Folder 10)
        - International AIDS Society Newsletter, 557242 (Reel 100, Box 129, Folder 11)
      - Plenary sessions, 557243 (Reel 99, Box 129, Folder 3)
      - Programme, 557244 (Reel 99, Box 128, Folder 1)
      - Related materials, circa 1993; 557245 (Reel 100, Box 129, Folder 12)
      - Reports, 557246
        - Jackman, Richard, 557247 (Reel 99, Box 129, Folder 5)
        - Medley, Raan, 557248 (Reel 99, Box 129, Folder 6)
        - Rygor, Robert, 557249 (Reel 100, Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Tenth International Conference on AIDS: The Global Challenge of AIDS: Together for the Future, Yokohama, Japan, 1994 Aug; 557250
      - Abstract book, vol. I-II, 557251 (Reel 100, Box 130, Folder 8-9)
      - Conference news, 557252 (Reel 100, Box 130, Folder 2)
      - Related material, 557253 (Reel 100, Box 130, Folder 1)
      - Second announcement and call for abstracts, 557254 (Reel 100, Box 129, Folder 13)
  - International Conference on AIDS in Africa/African Conference on Sexually Transmitted Diseases, 557255
    - Seventh International Conference on AIDS in Africa/Seventh African Conference on Sexually Transmitted Diseases, Yaounde, Cameroon, 1992 Dec 8-11; 557256
      - Correspondence, 557257 (Reel 100, Box 130, Folder 3)
      - Final program and abstract book, 557258 (Reel 100, Box 130, Folder 10)
      - Related materials about AIDS in Africa, 557259 (Reel 100, Box 130, Folder 6)
      - Reports, 557260
        - Rygor, Robert. A Report on the Seventh International Conference on AIDS in Africa., 557261; Report with photographs (Reel 100, Box 130, Folder 4)
        - World Health Organization. AIDS in Africa: Strategies for Its Prevention and Control., 1992 Jul; 557262 (Reel 100, Box 130, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous, 557263 (Reel 100, Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Eighth International Conference on AIDS in Africa/Eighth African Conference on Sexually Transmitted Diseases, Marrakech, Morocco, 1993 Dec 12-16; 557264
      - Call for abstracts and registration, 557265 (Reel 101, Box 131, Folder 1)
      - McDermott, James Thomas. The AIDS Epidemic in North Africa and the Middle East: Report to the Speaker of the House of Representatives. S.l: s.n., 1992; 557266 (Reel 101, Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Notes, 557267; See Series XV. Addenda for additional materials.
    - Carter, George M., 557268
      - HIV-Mediated Defects in Immune Regulation, 1993 Sep 29-30; 557269 (Reel 102, Box 133, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous, 1993 Feb; 557270 (Reel 102, Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, n.d.; 557271 (Reel 102, Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous conference publications, 557272
    - American Psychiatric Association. New Research Program and Abstract from the 139th Annual Meeting of the American Psychiatric Association in Washington, DC on May 10-16, 1986; 557273 (Reel 102, Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Health Education AIDS Liaison (HEAL). Fourth Series: "Is HIV Really the Cause of AIDS?" New York City, 1991; 557274 (Reel 101, Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Interscience Conference on Antimicrobial Agents and Chemotherapy. Program and Abstracts of the Thirty-Second Interscience Conference on Antimicrobial Agents and Chemotherapy: 11-14 October 1992, Anaheim Convention Center, Anaheim, California. Washington, 557275 (Reel 102, Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Laboratory of Tumor Cell Biology. [Abstracts and proceedings from the annual meeting of?] Laboratory of Tumor Cell Biology, National Cancer Institute. Bethesda, MD, 1988; 557276 (Reel 101, Box 131, Folder 10)
    - National Conference on HIV Infection and AIDS Among Racial and Ethnic Populations. Prevention & Beyond: A Framework for Collective Action. A National Conference on HIV Infection and AIDS Among Racial and Ethnic Populations, August 13-17, 1989. Washington, 557277 (Reel 101, Box 131, Folder 6)
- Series X. Published and near-print materials, 1969, 1982-1995, n.d; 557278; 58 boxes
  Series X. Published and near-print material is arranged in four subseries: X.A. Media, 1969, 1983-1995, n.d.; X.B. Journal articles, 1986-1989, n.d.; X.C. Near-print materials and assorted publications, 1982-1995, n.d.; and X.D. Newsletters and serials, 1982-1995, n.d. See Series XV. Addenda for additional materials.
  - X.A. Media, 1969, 1983-1995, n.d; 557279; 28 boxes
    Subseries X.A. Media contains primarily press clippings. ACT UP's Media committee was responsible for culling newspapers and magazines for articles about AIDS/HIV and related subjects. Some of these articles were made into media packets to be picked up by members at meetings. This subseries covers a broad range of subjects such as activism, discrimination, demonstrations, housing, medical treatments, and politicians. Combined with the clippings are notices of meetings and zaps, and miscellaneous ACT UP administrative materials.
    - 1969, 1983-1988 Jul, 557280 (Reel 103, Box 134, Folder 1-22)
    - 1988 Aug-Dec, 557281 (Reel 103, Box 135, Folder 1-3)
    - 1989 Jan-Aug, 557282 (Reel 104, Box 135, Folder 4-12)
    - 1989 Sep-Oct 15, 557283 (Reel 104, Box 136, Folder 1-4)
    - 1989 Oct 16-Dec, 557284 (Reel 105, Box 136, Folder 5-12)
    - 1990 Jan-Mar, 557285 (Reel 106, Box 137, Folder 1-12)
    - 1990 Apr-May 15, 557286 (Reel 106, Box 138, Folder 1-3)
    - 1990 May 16-Aug, 557287 (Reel 107, Box 138, Folder 4-14)
    - 1990 Aug-Sep, 557288 (Reel 107, Box 139, Folder 1-5)
    - 1990 Sep-Nov, 557289 (Reel 108, Box 139, Folder 6-10)
    - 1990 Nov-Dec, 557290 (Reel 108, Box 140, Folder 1-5)
    - 1990 Dec-1991 Mar, 557291 (Reel 109, Box 140, Folder 6-17)
    - 1991 Apr-Jul, 557292 (Reel 110, Box 141, Folder 1-11)
    - 1991 Aug-Sep, 557293 (Reel 111, Box 142, Folder 1-10)
    - 1991 Oct-Nov, 557294 (Reel 112, Box 143, Folder 1-11)
    - 1991 Dec-1992 Feb, 557295 (Reel 113, Box 144, Folder 1-14)
    - 1992 Feb-Apr, 557296 (Reel 114, Box 145, Folder 1-11)
    - 1992 Apr, 557297 (Reel 115, Box 145, Folder 12)
    - 1992 May-Jun, 557298 (Reel 115, Box 146, Folder 1-11)
    - 1992 Jul, 557299 (Reel 116, Box 146, Folder 12-14)
    - 1992 Aug, 557300 (Reel 116, Box 147, Folder 1-8)
    - 1992 Aug-Sep, 557301 (Reel 117, Box 147, Folder 9-14)
    - 1992 Oct, 557302 (Reel 117, Box 148, Folder 1-5)
    - 1992 Oct, 557303 (Reel 118, Box 148, Folder 6-12)
    - 1992 Nov, 557304 (Reel 118, Box 149, Folder 1-2)
    - 1992 Nov, 557305 (Reel 119, Box 149, Folder 3-10)
    - 1992 Dec-1993 Jan, 557306 (Reel 120, Box 150, Folder 1-12)
    - 1993 Jan-Feb, 557307 (Reel 121, Box 151, Folder 1-8)
    - 1993 Feb, 557308 (Reel 122, Box 151, Folder 9-12)
    - 1993 Mar, 557309 (Reel 122, Box 152, Folder 1-5)
    - 1993 Apr, 557310 (Reel 123, Box 152, Folder 6-11)
    - 1993 May, 557311 (Reel 123, Box 153, Folder 1)
    - 1993 May-Jun, 557312; Folders 8 and 9, covering June 1993, were not microfilmed. (Reel 124, Box 153, Folder 2-9)
    - 1993 Jul-Aug, 557313 (Reel 124, Box 154, Folder 1-7)
    - 1993 Aug-Sep, 557314 (Reel 125, Box 154, Folder 8-9)
    - 1993 Oct-Nov, 557315 (Reel 125, Box 155, Folder 1-8)
    - 1993 Nov-Dec, 557316 (Reel 126, Box 155, Folder 9-14)
    - 1994 Jan-Mar, 557317 (Reel 127, Box 156, Folder 1-13)
    - 1994 Apr, 557318 (Reel 127, Box 157, Folder 1)
    - 1994 Apr-Jul, 557319 (Reel 128, Box 157, Folder 2-11)
    - 1994 Aug, 557320 (Reel 128, Box 158, Folder 1-2)
    - 1994 Aug-Oct, 557321 (Reel 129, Box 158, Folder 3-11)
    - 1994 Nov-1995 Jan, 557322 (Reel 130, Box 159, Folder 1-10)
    - 1995 Feb-May, 557323 (Reel 131, Box 160, Folder 1-9)
    - 1995 May, 557324 (Reel 132, Box 160, Folder 10-11)
    - 1995 Jun-Oct, n.d, 557325 (Reel 132, Box 161, Folder 1-10)
    - Press kit, n.d.; 557326 (Reel 132, Box 161, Folder 11)
  - X.B. Journal articles, 1986-1989, n.d.; 557327; 2 boxes
    Subseries X.B. Journal articles consists of articles taken mainly from scholarly or medical journals focusing on AIDS/HIV issues.
    - Author, 557328
      - A-P, n.d.; 557329 (Reel 133, Box 162, Folder 1-21)
      - R-W, n.d.; 557330 (Reel 134, Box 163, Folder 1-5)
    - Journal of the American Medical Association (JAMA), n.d.; 557331 (Reel 134, Box 163, Folder 11)
    - Subject, 557332
      - AIDS/HIV, 557333
        - 1988-1989, 557334 (Reel 134, Box 163, Folder 7-8)
        - DNCB, 1986-1988; 557335 (Reel 134, Box 163, Folder 6)
      - Langerhans cells, 557336
        - n.d, 557337 (Reel 134, Box 163, Folder 9)
        - Related materials, n.d.; 557338 (Reel 134, Box 163, Folder 10)
  - X.C. Near-print materials and assorted publications, 1982-1995, n.d.; 557339; 14 boxes
    Subseries X.C. Near-print material and assorted publications contains directories, reports, sourcebooks, and miscellaneous pamphlets.
    - AIDS Information Sourcebook, 1991-1992; 557340; Directory of organizations (Reel 135, Box 164, Folder 1)